Here We Go Again people here we go
again we got another one as I said
another video I have an issue with
overindulgence so if I see one and I see
some others that like oh they should be
friends let me get them all the same
time that's what I'm going to do so here
we are here we are got another one okay
this one is Marina so let's go on and
get into it cut her open I said in
another video people open these and they
swear oh I can smell it
already I don't know what you're
smelling CU if it's packed well you
should not be able to smell that through
the wrapping you smelling something else
you smelling yourself so don't be
impacting these products with your own
sense stuff you got up your nose already
don't do that you can impact the product
review just my opinion nonetheless here
we go we're opening her
up
okay all right Marina what you're giving
to us it's all about the bottles right
now it's all about the bottles I'm
loving the bottles so we go oh she's so
adorable I like
her here she
is
Tada oh that's just too cute almost like
juice and y'all know we like us some
anyway all righty so Marina what are you
giving
Marina
no still can't smell it through the
bottle again y'all be saying that y'all
can smell it already double check like
go go smell some coffee beans or
something and then come back all right
because you may be impacting your review
so let's just open her up see what's
happening very subtle wait I'm kind of
subtle smell the cap too cuz that kind
of helps out okay well let's see what
she's
giving right
what we got Marina tell me something
good this one's a little
spicy
she you know perfume smell good when you
just want to close your eyes and let it
happen that's what's happening
yeah little fruity just a little bit of
spice
M I will go out with this one I would
yeah I will go out with this one so
again everybody this one was
Marina this is
her this is her luggage give her a try
yeah I think you'll like her so far they
have not gone wrong with these I have
seen some reviews that talk about they
have a musk scent so I would highly
recommend like if you're going through
Aroma Concepts take your time and
actually go to their site because they
take time to tell you the notes it's all
listed so you'll know what you're
getting so I that's how I did it I went
through their site yes they are in Tik
Tock shop but if you want the full
details check that out so you'll
understand hey does it have bergamont
does it have peaches does it have
grapefruit you know does to have a musk
it'll let you know so you won't be
caught off guard if you get it you're
not a person who in certain sense but
all of a sudden you got that scent so
check it out there but get it from Tik
Tock shop so they can get credit to the
Tik Tock
shop have you do it go on and get it
whatever you do you got to get you one
of these yes you
do